Guide to the John T. Yates, Jr. Papers, 1960-2015 UA.90.F106
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 2021 Addition, X.
  - Photographs - Pitt Surface Science Center Grand Opening, February 1983 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - Surface Science Center, 1983-2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Photographs - Surface Science Center Garden, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Photographs - Surface Science Center PhD Students "Weekend Gatherings", 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Photographs - Bob Tobin Birthday Party at Surface Science Center, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Photographs - Christmas Party, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Photographs - E.W Morley Award Symposium, May 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Photographs - International Field Emission Symposium, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Photographs - NATO Conference, September 1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Photographs - Yates Dinner, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Photographs - Summer, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Photographs - Surface Science Center Christmas Party, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Photographs - Kiev, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Photographs - Poland, June 1998 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Photographs - ACS Pittsburgh Award, October 22, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Photographs - Telluride Workshop, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Photographs - AVS Seattle, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Photographs - Oakland Holiday Inn Cocktail Party, August 18, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Photographs - Yates' 65th Birthday Symposium, August 19, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Photographs - Maui, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Photographs - Dinners at Pitt, 2006-2009 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Photographs - Hong Kong, October 2009 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Photographs - David Wayne Goodman (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Photographs - Italy Conference (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Photographs - Leybold–Heraeus Award (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Photographs - Margie Augenstein's Birthday Party (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Photographs - Mardi Gras Party (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Photographs - Surface Science Center PhD Students John and Kathy Russell's Wedding (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Photographs - Yates' Birthday (Box 9, Folder 51)